{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849018078","data":{"timestamp":" 947849018078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849024720","data":{"timestamp":" 947849024720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849031334","data":{"timestamp":" 947849031333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849038002","data":{"timestamp":" 947849038000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849044644","data":{"timestamp":" 947849044643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849052088","data":{"timestamp":" 947849052087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849063019","data":{"timestamp":" 947849063019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849069651","data":{"timestamp":" 947849069651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849077148","data":{"timestamp":" 947849077147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849083794","data":{"timestamp":" 947849083794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849091261","data":{"timestamp":" 947849091260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849102011","data":{"timestamp":" 947849102011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849108637","data":{"timestamp":" 947849108637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849116099","data":{"timestamp":" 947849116098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849122766","data":{"timestamp":" 947849122765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849129417","data":{"timestamp":" 947849129417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849136924","data":{"timestamp":" 947849136923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849149009","data":{"timestamp":" 947849149008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1c1c510d-3998-4337-8495-3826f518c1b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849180107","data":{"timestamp":" 947849180106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849186752","data":{"timestamp":" 947849186752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849194340","data":{"timestamp":" 947849194339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849200989","data":{"timestamp":" 947849200988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849208604","data":{"timestamp":" 947849208604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849219577","data":{"timestamp":" 947849219577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849225802","data":{"timestamp":" 947849225802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849232417","data":{"timestamp":" 947849232417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849239958","data":{"timestamp":" 947849239958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849246593","data":{"timestamp":" 947849246593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849254153","data":{"timestamp":" 947849254152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849264756","data":{"timestamp":" 947849264755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849271438","data":{"timestamp":" 947849271438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849278078","data":{"timestamp":" 947849278078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849285553","data":{"timestamp":" 947849285552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849292155","data":{"timestamp":" 947849292155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849298808","data":{"timestamp":" 947849298808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849306615","data":{"timestamp":" 947849306614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849324228","data":{"timestamp":" 947849324228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 496b7014-6cc3-4b15-a806-51c148227f2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849348625","data":{"timestamp":" 947849348624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849350993","data":{"timestamp":" 947849350992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849355759","data":{"timestamp":" 947849355759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849357527","data":{"timestamp":" 947849357526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849358687","data":{"timestamp":" 947849358686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849359731","data":{"timestamp":" 947849359730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849361978","data":{"timestamp":" 947849361978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849363085","data":{"timestamp":" 947849363085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849364069","data":{"timestamp":" 947849364069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849364974","data":{"timestamp":" 947849364973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849366487","data":{"timestamp":" 947849366487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" START_MASKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849369277","data":{"timestamp":" 947849369276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849370169","data":{"timestamp":" 947849370169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849372367","data":{"timestamp":" 947849372367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849374042","data":{"timestamp":" 947849374042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849378612","data":{"timestamp":" 947849378612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849380549","data":{"timestamp":" 947849380549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849381315","data":{"timestamp":" 947849381315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849383852","data":{"timestamp":" 947849383851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849385542","data":{"timestamp":" 947849385541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849385851","data":{"timestamp":" 947849385851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849387287","data":{"timestamp":" 947849387287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849389011","data":{"timestamp":" 947849389011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849389449","data":{"timestamp":" 947849389448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849390244","data":{"timestamp":" 947849390244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849390995","data":{"timestamp":" 947849390995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" MASKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849391784","data":{"timestamp":" 947849391784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849392477","data":{"timestamp":" 947849392477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849393419","data":{"timestamp":" 947849393418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849394292","data":{"timestamp":" 947849394291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" WAMEPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849394973","data":{"timestamp":" 947849394973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849399190","data":{"timestamp":" 947849399190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849403490","data":{"timestamp":" 947849403490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" START_WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849405182","data":{"timestamp":" 947849405181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849407047","data":{"timestamp":" 947849407047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" START_WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849408041","data":{"timestamp":" 947849408041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" START_ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849409771","data":{"timestamp":" 947849409771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849411633","data":{"timestamp":" 947849411633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849412425","data":{"timestamp":" 947849412425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849412759","data":{"timestamp":" 947849412759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849414077","data":{"timestamp":" 947849414077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849414648","data":{"timestamp":" 947849414647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849417776","data":{"timestamp":" 947849417776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849420301","data":{"timestamp":" 947849420301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849421286","data":{"timestamp":" 947849421286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849422265","data":{"timestamp":" 947849422265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849423259","data":{"timestamp":" 947849423259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849423307","data":{"timestamp":" 947849423307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849423539","data":{"timestamp":" 947849423539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849424110","data":{"timestamp":" 947849424109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849424299","data":{"timestamp":" 947849424298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849424528","data":{"timestamp":" 947849424527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849443320","data":{"timestamp":" 947849443320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849443409","data":{"timestamp":" 947849443409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" b5065bbe-961d-4d62-b136-3ca7cbd45ae0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849474515","data":{"timestamp":" 947849474514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849481142","data":{"timestamp":" 947849481142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849488703","data":{"timestamp":" 947849488703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849495390","data":{"timestamp":" 947849495390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849502995","data":{"timestamp":" 947849502995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849509647","data":{"timestamp":" 947849509647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849517190","data":{"timestamp":" 947849517190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849523852","data":{"timestamp":" 947849523851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849530502","data":{"timestamp":" 947849530501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849537164","data":{"timestamp":" 947849537164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849543825","data":{"timestamp":" 947849543824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849550482","data":{"timestamp":" 947849550481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849557139","data":{"timestamp":" 947849557138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849564589","data":{"timestamp":" 947849564589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849575571","data":{"timestamp":" 947849575571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849583396","data":{"timestamp":" 947849583395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1388322d-5d69-4b81-90dc-a12e8c931bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849607578","data":{"timestamp":" 947849607577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849614235","data":{"timestamp":" 947849614233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849620889","data":{"timestamp":" 947849620888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849627523","data":{"timestamp":" 947849627522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849634161","data":{"timestamp":" 947849634161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849640829","data":{"timestamp":" 947849640829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849648308","data":{"timestamp":" 947849648306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849654977","data":{"timestamp":" 947849654977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849661638","data":{"timestamp":" 947849661638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849668289","data":{"timestamp":" 947849668288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849674974","data":{"timestamp":" 947849674973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849682449","data":{"timestamp":" 947849682449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849694484","data":{"timestamp":" 947849694484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 251162cd-13a9-4723-bf3f-1525116e4968"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849708779","data":{"timestamp":" 947849708779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849709397","data":{"timestamp":" 947849709397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849709601","data":{"timestamp":" 947849709601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849710165","data":{"timestamp":" 947849710164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849711198","data":{"timestamp":" 947849711198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849711441","data":{"timestamp":" 947849711441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849712267","data":{"timestamp":" 947849712267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849712705","data":{"timestamp":" 947849712705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849713362","data":{"timestamp":" 947849713362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849716879","data":{"timestamp":" 947849716878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849729822","data":{"timestamp":" 947849729822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849730495","data":{"timestamp":" 947849730495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" START_PALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849732586","data":{"timestamp":" 947849732586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849733784","data":{"timestamp":" 947849733784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849734469","data":{"timestamp":" 947849734468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849735236","data":{"timestamp":" 947849735236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849735663","data":{"timestamp":" 947849735663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849736578","data":{"timestamp":" 947849736577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849738154","data":{"timestamp":" 947849738153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849739411","data":{"timestamp":" 947849739411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849739542","data":{"timestamp":" 947849739542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849740711","data":{"timestamp":" 947849740710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849742534","data":{"timestamp":" 947849742534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849743900","data":{"timestamp":" 947849743900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849744016","data":{"timestamp":" 947849744015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849746115","data":{"timestamp":" 947849746114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849746372","data":{"timestamp":" 947849746371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849747063","data":{"timestamp":" 947849747062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849747668","data":{"timestamp":" 947849747668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849748287","data":{"timestamp":" 947849748286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849749546","data":{"timestamp":" 947849749545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849752078","data":{"timestamp":" 947849752078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849756892","data":{"timestamp":" 947849756891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849756902","data":{"timestamp":" 947849756902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849761511","data":{"timestamp":" 947849761511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849762488","data":{"timestamp":" 947849762488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849762958","data":{"timestamp":" 947849762957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849766085","data":{"timestamp":" 947849766084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849768544","data":{"timestamp":" 947849768544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849771475","data":{"timestamp":" 947849771475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" START_MVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849774062","data":{"timestamp":" 947849774062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849775842","data":{"timestamp":" 947849775841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849777944","data":{"timestamp":" 947849777944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849779161","data":{"timestamp":" 947849779160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849783640","data":{"timestamp":" 947849783640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849785340","data":{"timestamp":" 947849785340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849787802","data":{"timestamp":" 947849787801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947849787907","data":{"timestamp":" 947849787907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142312"," gameId":" 1e77c05d-d6f5-4a40-be99-d09d8d0848c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}